GUY : I don 't wanna scare anyone ...
but I 'm gonna give it to you straight about Jason .
His body was never recovered from the lake after he drowned .
If you listen to the old-timers in town , they 'll tell you he 's still out there .
- Camp Crystal Lake is jinxed . - It 's got a death curse .
Some folks claim they 've even seen him ...
right in this area .
MAN : Who is that ?
Oh , hi . What are you doing out in this mess ?
The girl who survived that night at Camp Blood , that Friday the 13th ...
she claims she saw him .
The boy . Is he dead too ?
( GROWLING )
( SCREAMS )
We didn 't find any boy .
ALICE : Then he 's still there .
She disappeared two months later .
( CAT SNARLS )
( SCREAMS )
Legend has it that Jason saw his mother beheaded that night ...
( SCREAMING )
and he took his revenge .
( GASPS )
( SCREAMS )
( WHIMPERING )
A revenge that he 'll continue to seek if anyone enters his wilderness again .
( SCREAMING )
Jason was my son . And today is his birthday .
( SCREAMS )
That 's a good boy .
Good . Good Jason .
( SCREAMS )
Jason 's out there .
( BOTH GRUNT )
No ! Aah ! Aah !
( CHRIS WHIMPERING )
CHRIS : You can 't be alive !
Got another white coming in , Larry . Let 's keep the area clear .
MEDIC : Where are they ?
What do you need and where do you need it ?
We got ten of them . Yours is in the barn .
What 's wrong with him ?
He 's dead . Yeah , they 're all dead . You can pull it up over there .
- All dead . Some emergency . - Put her over there .
This the guy that 's been leaving the wet stuff ?
This time he got seven kids and three bikers .
This time they got him .
- VINCENT : Lainie ? - Hmm ?
- Belt him . - Yeah .
VINCENT : What 's the matter with you ? He 's dead .
MAN ( OVER LOUDSPEAKER ) : Okay , boys and girls , let 's get going !
God !
WOMAN ( OVER PA ) : Dr. Wellsely to O.R. 2 .
Here , sign it .
AXEL : Hmm ? Mm .
- This your last ? - No , got one more over there .
- Real cute girl . - Was .
She still is . All you gotta do is go over there ...
Nice talk . Real nice talk . I get the top copy .
- LAINIE : Take care , Axel . - Mm .
LAINIE : Man , he 's crazy .
( LAINIE SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY )
WOMAN ( OVER PA ) : Miss Aaron , telephone , please . Miss Aaron .
- I 'm free , doll . - And a bargain at twice the price .
- Hey . What 's the matter ? - I have a headache , Axel .
- For you , I always have a headache . - Oh , I can fix that .
Oh .
Meet me in the cold room .
I 'm closing up for the night . What do you say ? Okay ?
MORGAN : Axel , I am not going to fake any more orgasms for you .
You got the curse ?
If I do , you 're it .
Axel ?
( WHISPERS ) Axel .
( IN NORMAL VOICE ) Oh , Axel .
Axel ?
Aah ! God , Axel !
I 'm so glad you could come .
MORGAN : Axel , you are the Super Bowl of self-abuse !
I just came to watch the news .
MAN 1 ( ON TV ) : Now back to today 's news . The tragic story of mass slayings ...
( WHISTLES )
( MOUTHS ) I 'm sorry .
MAN 2 ( ON TV ) : And so begins yet another chapter in a story ...
most residents of Crystal Lake had prayed was over .
A trail of mangled bodies has finally led local authorities to conclude ...
( POP MUSIC PLAYING ON TV )
I really came to watch the news .
MAN 3 ( ON TV ) : We 're still awaiting positive identification of the body .
But to answer your question , yes , the man responsible ...
for the murders in Wessex County this past week ...
is at this moment in the Wessex County Medical Center morgue .
- Yeah ! - Hey .
That 's you they 're talking about on TV , pal .
I don 't believe you , Axel .
- Then ... shut ... my ... mouth . - My ... mouth .
MAN 2 : ... in the wake of what will always be known ...
as the Crystal Lake massacres . And now back to you , Bill .
( MORGAN SCREAMS )
Jesus Christmas !
Holy Jesus goddamn !
Holy Jesus jumping Christmas shit !
You better get that sucker in the icebox !
I must be nuts ! I mean , I really ...
- Good night , Axel . - Hey , where are you going ?
I 'll tell you where I 'm going , I 'm going crazy !
Shit ! Shit !
Hi , girls . Thanks for waiting .
Oh , no .
Shit !
( AXEL GROANING )
MORGAN : Get lost , Axel , I 'm busy . I 've had more than enough of you for one night .
Read my lips . Leave me alone ! Aah !
No !
( SCREAMING )
- I talked to Dad . - How is he ?
Oh . He said he was lonely . He asked me to come out and see him .
MRS. JARVIS : Did he tell you to take a number ?
No , but he asked about you .
Did he ?
Actually , you really should go out there to see him .
Yeah , I know .
MRS. JARVIS : I bet he could stand a visit .
What do you think ?
- TRISH : I think you 're getting horny . - MRS. JARVIS : Oh !
MRS. JARVIS : Tommy , turn that down !
Mom , I got 98,000 .
- How many robots is that ? - Thirty-five .
Now , why don 't you try killing a few more up in your room ?
TOMMY : I can 't . I need a bypass patch cord .
MRS. JARVIS : Maybe you can get one in town .
Trish will drive you .
Oh , honey , get a haircut , hmm ?
TOMMY : Oh , Ma .
- That 's a nice mask . - TOMMY : Do I have to get a haircut ?
You 're getting pretty terrific at making those things .
Thanks . I just customized it .
- Where 's Gordon ? - He went out .
Oh . Someone left the front door open .
We 're in the country .
Well , what happens if the psycho wanders in ?
TRISH : He 'd probably challenge him to a game of " Zaxxon . "
Hear any more about the place next door ?
Mm-hm . It 's been rented by some kids .
- Great . - How many ?
- Six . - It 'll be nice to have some company .
( TEENAGERS HUMMING UPBEAT TUNE )
TEENAGERS ( SINGING ) : Country boy , country boy
Sitting in the grass
Along came a prairie dog And crawled right up his ass
Ask me no more questions
You broke up with BJ Betty ?
So to speak . And would you lighten up on her ? She 's all right .
( CHUCKLES )
Yeah , I 'll say she 's all right .
( SIGHS )
You should have treated her right .
I mean , that girl wanted to be treated ... right .
I did . I did . I treated her right .
I treated her right . That 's what 's driving me so crazy .
I mean , first I would call her and she would take my calls ...
but she would have something that she 'd have to do .
And then she wouldn 't even take my calls .
I mean , can you figure that ? What the fuck happened ?
Let me put it in the old computer .
- No , I 'm serious about this . - Hey , the computer don 't lie .
Now , let 's see .
What ?
It says ...
It says you 're a dead fuck .
What ? A dead fuck ?
A lousy lay . You know ?
- A dead pecker . - JIMMY : Oh , I see .
Don 't hold it back from me , doc . I can take it .
- Give it to me straight . - I did not say it . The computer did .
- Yeah , well , there is no computer ! - Aha ! And there 's no Betty either .
Then I 'm a dead fuck .
Like I said , the computer don 't lie .
( SIGHS )
God , I 'm horny .
- Where are we now ? - Lost .
We are lost .
SAMANTHA : Pretty creepy , huh ?
Yeah .
All right , I think I got it .
Go straight ahead two miles and hang a right .
SAMANTHA : Paul , let 's pick her up .
PAUL : Sammy , where we gonna put her ?
TED : Hey , honey , you got a sister ?
Ruff , ruff !
( TWIG SNAPS )
( SCREAMS )
( GRUNTING )
TRISH : Oh , Mom , I thought we were having pizza .
I thought so too , honey , but we 've got a refrigerator full of leftovers .
You 're not smiling . You 're not in the mood for my tuna salad ?
- Well ... - I 'm not either .
I 'm in the mood for ...
- TOMMY : No . - MRS. JARVIS : Yes .
I feel like ...
- No ! - A Jarvis sandwich !
( ALL CHEERING AND CHATTERING )
- Wait , somebody 's at the door . - Oh , no , you don 't .
- No , Mom , I heard that too . - I 'll go .
Gordon ! Hey , Gordon . Where have you been , huh , Gordon ?
Have you been sneaking around ? Do you have a girlfriend or something ?
MRS. JARVIS : Tommy , close the door .
( BARKS )
Listen , Gordon , we 'll talk later .
( TEENAGERS CHATTERING )
All right .
- Hit me with the beer . - You got it .
- See ? What did I tell you ? - What ? You told me you were horny .
No , see , I 've come to realize that a guy can have a good time ...
without having to have girls all about .
That 's a sin , you dead fuck .
JIMMY : I really , really don 't want you to call me that anymore .
Aw .
( GORDON BARKING )
Hi . What a handsome mutt you are .
- His name 's Gordon . I 'm Trish . - Hi , Trish .
I don 't know how you do it .
Heh . I don 't know how you don 't .
I mean ...
you do it with everybody .
Oh , I do not !
I do it with Paul .
- Really ? - Come on , Sara !
You know how guys are . They lie about that all the time .
They say that about everybody .
They don 't say anything about me .
I mean , I don 't have ...
- Ha , ha . A reputation ? - I didn 't say that .
Oh . Look , I got my reputation in sixth grade .
Well , what does Paul think ?
Paul thinks I 'm great in bed , so that 's where I keep him . Ha , ha .
What are the sleeping arrangements here , anyway ?
Paul and I are taking the bedroom at the end of the hall ...
so you and Doug can sleep next door .
Really ?
Yeah . It 's okay , they 're bunk beds . Don 't worry about it .
I 'm gonna go to bed now , Mom . Good night .
Don 't forget , 6 a.m.
BOTH : Once around the lake .
Good night .
- MRS. JARVIS : Sleep well . - You too , Mom .
( GASPS )
( GRUNTING )
( SHRIEKS IN MUFFLED VOICE )
( DOOR CLOSES )
JIMMY : I think when we get into town I should give Betty a call .
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES )
Ted . Ted ?
I think ... I think when we get to town I should call Betty .
Jimbo , calling Betty is definitely a dead-fuck thing to do .
Look , first rule of love : Never get rejected by the same girl twice .
I mean , that 's useless . If you wanna make a fool out of yourself ...
always do it with someone new .
Well , I don 't know anybody new .
Well , sex is a great way to meet them .
Ooh . Oh , my !
( BOTH SHRIEK )
- Sorry . - Sorry .
- Don 't worry about it . - Hi .
Hi .
- You , uh ... You girls live around here ? - How far is it to Crystal Point ?
- Well , that 's where we 're going . - Yeah . It 's a long walk .
- We can take it . - I 'm going back to get the car .
- DOUG : Sara , do you want some company ? - This way ?
Thanks . I 'll just meet you guys there .
All right .
They 're cute .
Two of them . Two . Count them , one , two .
- Yes , yeah , and two of us . - TED : Exactly .
( GASPS )
( TED HOOTING )
Come on in ! Ha , ha .
Oh . No .
No , we ... we have no suits .
( TED HOOTS )
All right !
Skinny-dip ! Ah !
( TED HOOTS )
( BOTH LAUGH )
TED : Whoo ! Sam !
- TOMMY : Gordon , wait up ! - Gordon .
Gordon , wait up ! Wait a minute !
Gordon !
( ALL HOOTING )
- PAUL : Jimmy ! - Come on , Jimmy !
Come on , Jimmy !
( TEENAGERS LAUGHING AND HOOTING )
Whoa .
- Turn around . - Can 't I just ... ?
- Turn around ! - Trish , come on in !
No , thanks . I think I 'm overdressed .
- Hey , Trish ! - TRISH : Bye-bye .
TED : Party tonight !
TOMMY : Come on , Gordon , we 're too young for this .
Some pack of patootsies , huh ?
Tommy .
( ENGINE SPUTTERING )
TRISH : Oh , no .
What next ?
( ENGINE STOPS )
Can you fix it ?
- I need a screwdriver . - Maybe there 's one in the trunk .
I need the keys .
Thanks .
TRISH : Tommy , come on !
Come in , Sara , let 's see what you got .
- No . - Come on , Sara . Strip and dip .
Sam , I said no .
Well , then , I 'm gonna go under and stay under until you do .
See you later .
Sam ?
Sam !
God , Sam !
God .
Sam !
Sam ! Sam !
( SCREAMS )
Aah ! Samantha , you bitch !
- SAMANTHA : You like that ? - You bitch !
( GORDON WHIMPERING )
Turn it on , Trish .
( ENGINE SPUTTERING )
TOMMY : Turn it on !
- Whoa ! - Hi . Rob Dyer . Sorry about that .
- TRISH : Oh . Hello . - Hi . What 's your problem ?
- No problem . - I mean with the car .
TRISH : Oh , the car . Um , it won 't start .
Well , get in . Give it a crank .
Look , I 've tried everything already .
The only thing it could be is the solenoid .
If you had a screwdriver ...
ROB : Okay , give it a crank .
( ENGINE SPUTTERING )
( ENGINE STARTS )
You need a lift ?
I didn 't think anyone lived this deep in the woods .
We do . What are you hunting for up here ?
Bear . Anybody up at the lake today ?
You can 't be hunting for bear .
How about kids ? There any kids , vacationers , people like that ?
Yeah . A bunch of kids moved in yesterday . Right next door to us .
- TRISH : This is it . - ROB : Thanks for the lift .
( ENGINE STOPS )
Gordon !
Would you like to come in for a minute ?
I don 't think I can .
TOMMY : Well , you gotta come in .
Come on , I got something real neat to show you up in my bedroom .
Hi , Mom !
MRS. JARVIS : Tommy , who 's your friend ?
Mom , this is Rob . Rob , this is my mother .
- Hello , Mrs ... - MRS. JARVIS : Jarvis .
Amazing .
Come here , I wanna show you something .
( TOMMY GROWLING )
( LION 'S " LOVE IS A LIE " PLAYING ) No way , not tonight , no way
Not today
- Just ' cause you play it cool - JIMMY : Would you care to dance ?
- To this ? - It 's good .
All right
JIMMY : Oh , well , good .
Don 't ask me to stay
Don 't think you got it made No , no
You 're wrong
- ( LAUGHING ) - ' Cause you can 't fake it anymore
I know what you 're waiting for
I should turn away And walk right out that door
Because I know love ...
JIMMY : Hey , how come you turned that off ?
PAUL : Relax , Jimbo . You 're gonna love this .
( JOHNNY MERCER 'S " TANGERINE " PLAYING ON STEREO )
Wanna give Teddy bear a kiss ?
Heh . Mm ! Teddy . Teddy , uh ...
I 've gotta get another drink .
With her eyes of night
- Excuse me . - You like this stuff ?
TINA : You like slow dancing ?
Tangerine
I could learn to .
Kiss me , you fool .
- Certainly . - SAMANTHA : Ha , ha .
Uh , maybe we could dance to this one .
Come on , let Teddy bear show you how it 's done .
Stay near the trail .
- It goes all the way around the lake . - Yeah , I will .
- There 's only three of you up here ? - Mm-hm .
My parents have separated . You know , middle-aged crazies . Heh .
I kind of hope they get back together .
Yeah , I hope so too .
( TRISH SIGHS )
- Looks like another rainy one , huh ? - Yeah .
Listen , if it gets too bad out there ...
or if you wanna take a shower or whatever , we 're always home .
And if we 're not , Tommy usually leaves the door open .
- Good night . - Take care .
TED : Hey , how you doing with yours ?
Nowhere , huh ?
Check .
You gotta warm her up . Watch me . Do what I do .
And , Jimbo , don 't be such a dead fuck .
I told you . I told you that I didn 't like that .
- Besides , you 've got the hot one . - Check .
- Hi . - He thinks that 's funny .
He thinks that 's a funny thing he 's doing .
( ALL CHEERING )
( ALL CHATTERING )
- Okay , you ready , Tina ? On three . - All right .
- PAUL : One ! - SARA : One !
ALL : Two !
ALL : Three !
( ALL CHEERING )
PAUL : And the winner is ... Tina !
DOUG : All right !
( ALL CHATTERING )
TINA : What do I win ?
What do you want ?
Jimbo , put on another record .
TED : Jimbo .
You don 't mind , do you ?
Actually , I was thinking about taking a little swim .
It seems to be getting a bit close in here for me .
- SARA : Sam ... - Sara . Sara , let 's dance .
I don 't wanna dance .
Well , let 's mind our own business .
( TONY MARTIN 'S " TO EACH HIS OWN " PLAYING ON STEREO )
Look , I 'll talk to Paul .
All right ?
( BOTH CHUCKLE )
TINA : Mm .
- I wanna talk to you for a second . - Man , I am going to kill him .
- I said I wanted to talk to you for a second . - Not now , dead fuck .
That 's what I wanted to talk to you about .
Do you believe this guy ?
- I mean , I had her . She was mine . - Oh .
Well , you know what I suggest you do about that , Teddy ?
I think you should run that through your little computer .
( TWIG SNAPS )
Paul ?
I know you 're out there , Paulie .
( TWIG SNAPS )
SAMANTHA : Paul ?
Okay . Screw you , Paulie .
Come on , Paul .
I know you 're out there .
Paul ?
Screw you , Paul .
( SCREAMING )
Look , what 's the matter ?
I can 't go through with this .
I 'm sorry . I gotta go .
( LEAVES RUSTLE )
( ON STEREO ) What good is a song
If words just don 't belong ?
You wanna dance ?
Yeah . Yeah .
No good alone
To each his own
For me there 's you
If a flame is to grow
I thought that you wanted to be with Ted .
Well , I did .
But now I wanna be with you .
( BOTH CHUCKLE )
That makes me feel like a rat .
Two lips must insist
On two more to be kissed
Well , do you wanna join them ?
Jimmy .
Why don 't we just go upstairs ?
Upstairs . Heh .
Ahem . That 's a teddy bear . Wanna give Teddy bear a kiss ?
PAUL : Fuck !
( PAUL SCREAMING )
( TWIG SNAPS )
Shit .
This is ... This is a neat room .
This is your room .
No . Actually , it 's Paul 's room .
You 're neat .
( SCREAMS )
( BOTH LAUGHING )
- JIMMY : Oh , what a shock . - Sorry .
Hey , you guys ! Look what I found .
( TED LAUGHING )
SARA : What is that ?
( ALL LAUGHING )
God , what a pig !
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
Tina ? We gotta go .
You go .
Tina , I 'm gonna leave without you .
Take an umbrella .
( THUNDER CRASHING )
TERRI : You slut !
( TERRI WHIMPERING )
( LAUGHING )
I 'm going upstairs .
You tired ?
No .
Do you mind sleeping in the bottom bunk tonight ?
Why , you wanna sleep on the top ?
No .
( SARA CHUCKLES )
Give me a few minutes .
Okay ?
Good night , Teddy bear . Ha , ha .
Good night .
- Ha , ha . - Stop .
Tommy ? I 'm gonna towel off and then I 'm gonna strangle you .
Tommy ? Trish ?
( LIGHT SWITCH CLICKING )
Anybody home ?
Gordon ?
Where 's Tommy ?
Where 's Trish ?
Matter of fact , where the hell are you ?
Gordon ?
( THUNDER CRASHING )
( GASPS )
Watch it !
Can we slow down a little ? The party 's gonna go on all night .
I think I 'm gonna lose my lollipop .
TRISH : Mom , we 're home .
Mom ?
- Where is she ? - I don 't know .
TRISH : Mom ?
( LIGHT SWITCH CLICKING )
- She 's not here . - Maybe she 's still jogging .
TRISH : She 's never gone this long . And in the rain ?
- I 'm going out on the path . - Me too .
No , you stay here in case she comes back .
- I 'll go ! - Stay here and fix the lights .
( TWIG SNAPS )
( GASPS )
- What the hell are you doing here ? - What are you trying to do , kill me ?
Tina ? Ahem .
TINA : Hmm ?
Never mind .
Tell me .
Um ...
Did I ... ? Was , um ... ?
Was I ... ?
Was I a dead fuck ?
( TINA CHUCKLES )
- What ? - A dead fuck .
No .
You , uh ... ? You know what I think ?
You know what I really think ?
I think you were incredible .
( JIMMY CHUCKLES )
- And I wanna do it again . - Yeah .
Don 't you move . I 'll be right back .
TED : Oh . Ha-ha-ha .
Check it out .
Why don 't you run this through your computer , Teddy bear ?
Hey , congratulations , Jimbo .
JIMMY : Where 's that bottle of wine ? Why don 't we celebrate ?
TED : I think maybe I drank it .
( BOTH LAUGHING )
I was great !
I was great . I was great .
Love , Teddy bear !
L-O-V-E .
Hey , Ted , where is ... ? Where is that corkscrew ?
That fancy corkscrew for the wine bottle ?
Ted ?
( LAUGHS )
JIMMY : Hey !
Ted ? Ted ! Hey , Ted , where the hell is the corkscrew ?
Jimmy ?
My sister Sandra was a really great kid .
But the man that killed your sister is dead .
No , he 's alive .
Look .
Jason as a child , right ?
Artist 's conception of Jason as described by a would-be victim , right ?
And then the murders .
But he 's dead .
Jason 's body has disappeared from the morgue .
- It was stolen . - It was not stolen .
Two people at the hospital are missing . This is coincidence ?
He 's alive .
Oh , my God . Tommy 's at the house .
( LAUGHS )
Ha , ha . Teddy .
Oh , man .
Oh .
Oh . Ha , ha .
( CHUCKLING )
So you wanna give the old Teddy bear a kiss ?
Jimbo ?
( CHUCKLES )
( GASPS )
DOUG : Sara , I think I 'm in heaven .
I think I 'm in love .
What ?
I 'll meet you in the bottom bunk .
DOUG ( SINGING ) : Tangerine , she is all they claim
With her eyes of night
And lips as bright as flame
Tangerine
( DOUG SINGING INDISTINCTLY )
She is
Sara ? Change your mind ?
Come on . Get in here .
There 's plenty of room . We can sing a duet .
Who is it , Paulie ?
Paulie .
Hey , Paulie , is that you ?
Hey , Paulie . Whoops . Dropped my bar of soap , old buddy .
Lucky you ain 't in here with me , old pal .
Ho-ho-ho .
( GRUNTING )
I came to hear you sing .
So sing .
( GASPS )
Aah ! Sam ! Samantha !
Sam ! Sam ! Sam !
Sand !
Sam ! Sam !
( GRUNTING )
( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
TRISH : Oh , Tommy . Thank God you 're okay .
- Oh , Tommy . - What happened ?
- Where 's Mom ? Is she back ? - No , not yet .
TRISH : I 'm gonna call for help .
TOMMY : Rob , what 's going on ?
- I 'm not getting anything . - I wanna go next door .
- TRISH : I 'm going with you . - No .
TRISH : I 'm going with you .
- You stay here and lock the door . - Tommy , hold the fort .
TRISH : Gordon !
- ROB : He 's been here . - TRISH : Wait . What if he still is here ?
Take this . Take it .
I 'm going downstairs . You stay right here with Gordon .
- TRISH : No . - Stay right here with Gordon .
( GORDON WHIMPERING )
Gordon .
Gordon !
Gordon ?
( GORDON WHIMPERS )
( SCREAMING )
Rob ! Rob , he 's here ! He 's here !
Rob ! Rob !
( SCREAMING )
Rob ! Rob ! Rob !
Rob , he 's here ! He 's here .
- He 's killed all of them , I know it . - ROB : Come one , come on .
Shit . Give me a hand .
- Gotta get the knife . - No ! No . No !
ROB : Oh , my God !
( SCREAMS )
( ROB SCREAMING )
Oh , God , he 's killing me ! He 's killing me !
Run , Trish ! Run ! Trish !
( SCREAMING )
( ROB SCREAMS )
ROB : Trish , run !
( ROB SCREAMING )
( WHIMPERING )
( SOBBING )
( SCREAMING )
No ! Get off me !
( PANTING )
( GASPING )
( GLASS SHATTERING )
( SCREAMS )
TRISH : Tommy !
- All the doors locked ? - Yes .
TRISH : Go get me a hammer and nails right now .
- TOMMY : Is he here ? - Yes .
Tommy , hurry !
( TRISH SCREAMS )
( TOMMY SCREAMS )
TOMMY : Help me ! Help me !
Help me ! Help me ! Let me go !
Help me ! Put me down ! Put me down !
Tommy , help me push this .
Where is he ?
( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
What 's he doing ? What 's he doing ?
( BOTH GASP )
( BOTH WHIMPERING )
( GRUNTING )
( WHISPERING ) Listen , Tommy , I 'm gonna get him out of the house .
And when I do , I want you to run like hell , do you hear me ?
Run like hell , okay ?
Oh , my God !
( TRISH SCREAMS )
- Trish ! - TRISH : Tommy , no !
Trish !
( TRISH SCREAMING )
TOMMY : Trish !
Tommy ?
Tommy , you were supposed to leave !
Tommy ! Tommy , get the hell out of here !
No !
You son of a bitch .
I 'm gonna give you something to remember us by .
( JASON GRUNTS THEN GROWLS )
( SCREAMING )
Jason !
Remember me , Jason ?
Jason , don 't you remember ?
Remember , Jason ?
Jason , remember ?
Remember ?
( WHIMPERING )
( GASPING )
( SCREAMING )
( JASON GROANS )
TRISH : Tommy .
( BOTH CRYING )
TRISH : Tommy !
( GRUNTING )
Tommy !
Die !
- Die ! - TRISH : Tommy !
- TRISH : Tommy ! - TOMMY : Die !
The shoulder will need some surgery .
But we can wait till she 's a better candidate .
Now , you just get a good rest , young lady .
You haven 't answered my question .
Neither one of you is answering my question .
Often , during extreme duress , people are capable ...
of extraordinary behavior .
That 's what happened when your brother violently attacked the killer .
At that moment it was perfectly normal for him to act to protect himself .
He 's going to be just fine .
But right now , what you need is rest .
Can I see my brother now ?
Sure . But only for a minute .
I 'll send him in .
( WHISPERS ) Tommy .
( English - US - SDH )